frisgo.com 2009-03-24

# Privacy Policy

Frisgo.com, and its advertisers and partners are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

#### Consumer Information

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Frisgo.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Frisgo.com or it's partners may obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). Any information collected by Frisgo.com is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

If you would like additional information about the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by Frisgo.com please contact us at [support@frisgo.com](mailto:support@frisgo.com).  

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Frisgo.com may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Frisgo.com may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

#### Data Collection and Opt Out

Frisgo.com, as well as most sites on the Internet, may use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Frisgo.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Frisgo.com serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Frisgo.com target ads to you. This cookie can help Frisgo.com ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Frisgo.com to deliver you an ad. 

We allow advertisers and other third parties to place cookies onto your computer when you visit this website. These cookies are placed to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting this website, as well as your web surfing behavior on this website and other websites you may visit. That information is used to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other websites, and/or to keep track of your response to each ad. If you would like to know more about these practices and your choices about not having this information used to target ads to you, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

If you have any additional questions about Frisgo.com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [support@frisgo.com](mailto:support@frisgo.com).
